LARA ZEGART

laraezegart@gmail.com

STATEMENT

I am working to continue to develop my skills, extend my experience in a hands-on and motivating environment, and meet new people. My goal is to continue working in full stack web development in order to create purposeful and helpful web applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Client-side storage
- Node.js
- Responsive frameworks

ADDITIONAL SKILLS & HIGHLIGHTS

- Conflict Resolution
- Project Management & Development
- Strategic Planning
- Collaborative Leader
- Strong Communicator
- Organized
- Motivated
- Positive
- Community Development
- Bilingual in French; Basic Conversational in Spanish
- Theatre Experience; Stage Manager, Technical Director, Designer

EDUCATION

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp. In progress; September 2020-March 2021.

UC Berkeley Extension.

Master of Arts Honours French and Comparative Literature. June, 2016.

University of St. Andrews.

St. Andrews, Scotland.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tamalpais Community Services District:

July 2020 - Present Park and Recreation Coordinator

January 2019 Recreation Supervisor

September 2016 Event staff

West America After Care:

July 2017 - Present Co-owner, managing member, and Director

September 2016 Student Tutor and Supervisor

Terra Marin School:

June 2018 - June 2019 Humanities Teacher, 5th-8th grade

Ring Mountain Day School:

August 2017 - June 2018 Math Teacher, 6th & 7th grade

August 2016 - June 2017 Substitute Teacher, K-8th, all subjects